Just.
-And we also spice up.
I try to be my best self.
Happy, nice, smells good and everything.
So I'm not really myself to a hundred percent either.
But then you come to that stage then hopefully ...
Most often.
-... turns into a lasting love.
From this by spiceing up
To be able to sit in cozy pants and not care for being chosen.
You are confident that you have been chosen.
-Just.
This is when you can think that these differences are starting to appear more.
Because you often have much more sex during love, that's the usual.
But in the love relationship there are other things that become important.
You feel rejected if you take the initiative and the other pressed.
But we have control over it and yet choose to try
So hopefully it will not be such a big thing if it does not succeed.
No, and I think it's important, just as you say now
That if I'm on green and you on yellow, I need to scan myself a little.
If we have a cozy moment and try to work on finding your desire
What it is now, and it just doesn't appear-
Can I still feel that we have had a cozy moment and it is totally okay.
But if I have had a tough day at work or have struggled with some child
Then maybe I, if we can't find your desire, feel dismissed.
Then it is better not to be at that time.
Now that we've talked so much about lust
it may be important to re -connect to the needs map.
But it is not in family.
-Why?
Well, there we need to come back to this with having slightly different roles.
In the Viet you are love partners, where it becomes a natural connection.
There, intimacy can be and thrive.
But in family, the roles are that we are parents.
That association or contact with desire does not appear when you are a family.
We often see that there can be a crash, not least when the kids are so small
That someone is parental worker and the other works outside the home.
It may be a little easier for the person who is not parenting
To have had a I-time to find the entrance to the desire in the couple relationship.
But anyone who is parental is in their parenting role.
But this can often be a yellow position for the parental working.
The child has just fallen asleep
But the parent who at the time in life has taken on responsibility for this-
Has like that parental antenna turned on and is in parenthood.
Therefore, it can be so difficult that it is just "pang" to be turned off.
It's not that easy.
No, and also that it may be quickly turned on if you hear a little whine.
It is very important to think about.
Then we will talk about having a few different entrances to sex.
For some, six is six, that is, that is when we are closest.
But some other of us may need to have closeness before we have sex.
Here it is not uncommon for couples to be different.
One is no more right or wrong
But we need to know how we work-
For the goal is the same, the goal is for us to be close to each other.
Where the incoming, lust -enhancing part is also the mysterious part, so ...
But that does not mean that you should not be able to talk about it.
What I mean is that some things need to be a little mysterious.
Some fantasies should not always share
But some things we need to share, especially what we have been talking about now.
Expectations, that you may need time, that you have different entrances and so on.
I also think, based on this with rejection, that if you take an initiative
It becomes important that I not only turn your back, but say:
"I know you want to, but I'm not there. Can we just hug"
Then you don't have to feel rejected.
At the same time I think that if I want to go for a walk and you don't want to
That we can actually be physical with each other without having an expectation of sex.
But we may need to hug and take each other in everyday life.
There you have a thing you usually say that we finally say.
That about everyday life.
It is actually that if I am at home with the baby who needs a lot of physical closeness
and maybe also ammar-
So I get a lot of the need for contact.
There is a lot of skin to skin all day.
So I don't have much need for the other in it.
But you have it, because you have not received your contact need.
There you may need to remember to save a little.
Not so that one should reject the child
But one may need to think that you have not received as much-
As I have received, who have been home.
So save the hug.
-Save a hug.
Or two.
Or three, maybe.
You decide that.
Important to consider: you have different desires in different periods.
Do not compare with love.
The driving force must be desire.
Think about what is lust -lowering and lust enhancing
And share it with your partner.
You often have different entrances to sex.
For someone can sex lead to closeness
And for the other, the emotional proximity can come before and lead to sex.
It was all the clips.
-Feel free to go back and look again.
You have found them via our website and there is also contact details
If you want to check something with us or contact some calls.
We also have a Facebook page you can follow, where we put things out every now and then.